<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[OnyroHealing]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[OnyroHealing]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:32:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[why would people want to receive a healing?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>why would people want to receive a healing?</h1><p></p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/why-would-people-want-to-receive-a-healing/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">32960c55-3c97-4e16-a8f9-17d565d87b56</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the healing works..]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How the healing works..</h1><p></p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/how-the-healing-works/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dc82cc76-43a4-4e6a-a5fd-bc62018c2045</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:27:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[So how do we Tap into These Frequencies?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>So how do we Tap into These Frequencies?</h1><p>We can Tap into Different vibrational Frequencies by first taping into our emotions. now that sounds easier than done.. so how do you tap into your emotions?? lets first start by our 5 senses, touch, smell, taste, hearing and seeing. Ok.. So now lets start with my favourite one.. Seeing, you can start with your favourite one…. I am an artist that used to paint a lot. So I used to love looking at all the tiny details of the things that are around me. like the little line on the table that your sitting, the little holes on your computer or smart phone. try to see the smallest detail that your eyes can see. Focus is the Key here. Focus on just Seeing The Smallest Detail possible. Don’t worry if you can’t see the smaller detail just go to your best capability, the point is not being able to see the smaller detail but to tap into The Zone. Be Fascinated by what your seeing. Be amazed of the small intricate Details and be in a state of questioning of wonderment and Curiosity. If that doesn’t satisfy you than go to another Sense. Lets Go with Hearing…. Listen to Everything…. Again the key is focus, curiosity, amazement, Wonderment. Listen to the silence.. listen to the noises in your house, listen to the noises outside… and again be amazed… How is all this possible? how are we capable of listening, and seeing…. and if your thinking, well... its because of the sound emits sound waves that travels to the ears and than is decoded by the brain… well yes but how ?? how can we do all that without thinking ? how come our subconscious mind is capable of doing that? always bring that wonderment to the next level. these are unanswerable questions. and even if we do find another answer there will always be more questions right after.. we will never find all the answers.. How ? why ? don’t try to answer the questions.. just be amazed by its possibility. try these with all of the senses… </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/d963b9ed-1520-4733-a5d1-04aadb218675/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d963b9ed-1520-4733-a5d1-04aadb218675</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:14:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Story]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>My Story</h1><p>I first started learning this through my friend Alex Tchaparian. One day he came to work on my lower back as a massage therapist, than he said i want to try something new, he started waving his hands around my lower back area, after like 5 min of doing that he told me to test my lower back and see if it hurts… I tried and Guess what.. it was Healed !!! I was super Excited ! i didn’t know what happened.. but all i knew is that i had to learn how to do that. and so our journey began. he became like a mentor to me and he showed me how to tap into these frequencies. after 7 years of learning. We also did a seminar called recollective healing which helped me learn the frequencies that we were using a bit more. When people ask me whats the name of your technique… to be honest there is no Name for it.. cause its Not a technic.. Eric Pearl calls it the Recollective Healing.. But i guess we can use that name to call the frequencies we Tap into.  Recollective Healing Frequencies. And we just Tap into it to play in it and to be guided by it.  </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/my-story/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4645851e-1aaf-4f2c-959e-dcd2bd116ff3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:08:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vibration and frequencies]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Vibration and frequencies</h1><p></p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/onyrohealing/vibration-and-frequencies/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c336ad87-9c6e-416e-9beb-028068306601</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 19:11:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>